here's the sum of the first n positive
squares like you've never seen them
before as the levels get higher the
visual proofs get
Wilder turn it
up turn it
up turn
it sometimes it's good to
whisper and keep your voice down
low but sometimes you got to risk it and
let the whole world
know don't want to be too
quiet I'd rather get real
loud we going to start a
riot come on show you
how let's get a little bit
louder let's get a little bit
louder got to get a little bit
louder let's get a little bit turn it up
let's just see how high we can go turn
it up no stopping till we lose our
control turn it up until we feel it down
in our
soul let's get your heartbeat
pumping this is the honest truth this is
the honest truth if we get these bodies
jumped we're going to shake it Loose
Shake It
Loose let's get a little bit like
Lou let's get a little bit
louder got to get a little bit
louder let's get a little bit turn it up
let's just see how high we can go turn
it up no stopping till we lose our
control turn it up until we feel it down
in our soul turn it
up turn it up let's just see how high we
can go turn it up no stop until we lose
our control turn it up until we feel it
down in our soul turn it
up let's get a little bit
louder let's get a little bit
louder got to get a little bit
louder let's get a little
bit let's get a little bit
louder let's get a little bit louder
let's go come on got get a little bit
louder
yeah let's get a little
bit turn it up let's just see how high
we can go turn it up don't stop until we
lose our control turn it up until we
feel it down in our soul turn it
up turn it up let's just see how high we
can go turn it up no stop until we lose
our control turn it up until we feel it
down in our soul turn it
up
turn it up let's just see how high we
can go turn it up don't stop until we
lose our control turn it until we feel
it down in our soul turn
it comment down below which level is
your
favorite